[{
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Administration is all about planning, organizing, and guiding a group of people to achieve a _______ goal.",
    "answer": "common"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Theo Haimann defined administration as the overall determination of _______ and setting of major objectives.",
    "answer": "policies"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Goals are the desired outcomes or the _______ that everyone works toward.",
    "answer": "big picture"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "The _______ structure in administration ensures there is a leader to guide decisions and resolve conflicts.",
    "answer": "authority"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Management is the process of handling _______ like people, money, and time to achieve goals efficiently.",
    "answer": "resources"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Mary Parker Follett defined management as the art of getting things done through _______.",
    "answer": "others"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Management involves planning ahead, organizing resources, giving directions, ensuring teamwork, and keeping things on track, according to _______.",
    "answer": "Henry Fayol"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Planning, organizing, staffing, directing, and _______ are key aspects of management.",
    "answer": "controlling"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "An _______ is a structured group of people working together to achieve specific goals.",
    "answer": "organization"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Organizations are intentionally created to achieve specific goals, such as _______, delivering services, or solving problems.",
    "answer": "producing goods"
  }
]
